(This story is entirely fictional)
We used to write to each other.
Those were good times, right?
It wasn't happiness.
It was my only support
after my dad died.
(Based on novel Doctor Qin: Executer)
Actually, I asked you out that night
to confess my feelings.
(Ten years ago)
Qin,
it's raining this hard.
Looks like your plans are shot.
Why not try another way to confess?
Just write her a love letter,
then tuck a flower petal inside.
I'll make sure it gets to her!
It's just a passing shower
with southerly winds at Force 5.
The rain clouds have almost blown away.
It'll definitely clear up after eight.
Awesome!
(Fireworks)
Qin,
I won't question
your weather forecast.
But when it comes to girls,
you still have a lot to learn.
Your dad's not around
to keep tabs on you,
but I need to get home now.
Any later
and my dad will kill me!
Jin Keke isn't coming tonight.
Light it.
(That night,)
(I kept waiting for you.)
(Longfan University Affiliated
High School Dropout Certificate)
(You left without saying a word.)
(I was pretty upset.)
(Tell me...)
(If all that had never happened,)
(would we...)
Officer Qin.
You'd better head back now.
You've got cases to solve tomorrow.
=Doctor Qin: Executer=
=Episode 15=
All of Qiao Shengchan's
social connections
have been cut off.
Liu Sanhao, the only one
who knew his family, is dead too.
Now he's vanished completely.
(Notes)
Unless there's a special reason,
Qiao Shengchan,
a well-behaved ex-con,
has no need to hide.
Su Shi, Le Tianyi,
Liu Sanhao, Zhang Xiaodong...
and now Qiao Shengchan is missing too.
(Notes)
Maybe the so-called Executer
has a hit list?
We're now racing
against a ghost
we can't even see.
(Retribution has come.
Every sin will be paid for.)
They have the upper hand on everything:
the time, the place, and the target.
And we're
always one step behind.
(Weiyou Mart)
Liu Sanhao is dead.
What?
You already told me that.
But we found out
your father's death
was connected to Liu Sanhao.
Do you think
I have a motive to kill him?
Are you investigating me now?
That's right.
I hated him.
I dreamed of seeing him dead.
But, Qin Ming,
my dad wasn't the only one
driven to death
by Liu's loan shark debts.
Those who want him dead
could line up around the block.
Who am I to them?
Well,
if people cheered over his death,
let me tell you this:
I'd definitely be one of them.
Besides,
my dad died a long time ago.
He's nothing but ashes now.
But I still have to live.
Revenge?
That's the kind of thing
you see in movies.
Sounds great,
but for a nobody like me,
I don't have the ability,
or the energy for it.
(Weiyou Mart)
The last skewer.
If we lose touch again,
would you still wait this long
to find me?
(Weiyou Mart)
Hello, Han.
There are quite a few in town
who won't be sleeping tonight.
Got it.
Keke,
I have to go back for a meeting.
I'll come back and pick you up.
Qin Ming,
I'm not waiting for you this time.
We found the drone fragments,
but there's only so much footage
we can recover.
This is the first recovered segment.
The person's decisive and strong.
They likely have experience
with violent crimes.
There's another accomplice!
(Ah!)
(Help!)
That's all the footage we recovered.
Under our tight surveillance,
how could the killers commit the murder
on the rooftop?
We searched the entire building,
but found no one suspicious.
We must've missed something.
I just thought of something.
There was a case before
where the crime scene
was in Building One.
We searched the entire building
and came up empty-handed.
Finally, we realized
the killer had accessed there
through Building Two.
How did they get there?
The rooftops are connected.
Liang, we found something.
The tenant of Unit 1705 next building
is Qiao Shengchan.
Move! Go get him!
(Retribution has come.
Every sin will be paid for.)
Keke!
Welcome.
Where's Jin Keke?
Who's Jin Keke?
The manager called me
to cover the shift.
I don't know who you're talking about.
(You must be tired too.)
(We're all tired.)
(Do you think
I have a motive to kill him?)
(Are you investigating me now?)
(There's another accomplice!)
(Shengchan!)
(Buddy.)
Bro.
Nine years.
The best nine years of my life
are going to be wasted here.
What nonsense!
How can you say
they're the best nine years?
Once you get out,
the good years will just be starting.
But my wife and my mom...
With no man at home,
they'll just get bullied.
Enough.
Look at you,
getting all sentimental.
Bro, I've worked for you
all these years.
I mean,
you can't just abandon them.
Since you call me your brother,
how could I abandon them?
How could I let them be mistreated?
From now on,
your mother
will be like my own mom,
and your wife will be...
like my own sister.
All right?
Buddy, you...
I... I was wrong.
Please let me go.
I'm begging you!
I was wrong!
You've harmed too many people.
Do you remember Jin Qingshan?
He borrowed 80,000 from you.
He paid for three years,
100,000 a year,
and still owed you 500,000.
You forced his daughter
to work for Zhang Xiaodong
with her father's life.
You knew that once she was there,
she'd have to endure
the most desperate time of her life,
didn't you?
I... I was just the middleman!
He was the sick one.
He liked watching girls
do whatever he said.
I only found girls for him.
I never touched them.
I really didn't touch them.
I never touched them...
I... I'm sorry about your dad.
Shengchan, I'm sorry!
What do you want from me?
I'm begging you!
Please...
When Jin Qingshan died, do you know
what was troubling his daughter?
No... I don't know.
She was thinking,
after she'd already worked
for Zhang Xiaodong,
and done all those disgusting things,
why her father still had to die!
(Innovate and Renew)
She couldn't figure it out.
(Xiaoxue...)
(I'm sorry.)
Some people
don't deserve to be called human.
Dad...
Dad!
(Miss,)
(are you okay?)
I'm fine.
Dad...
I've avenged you.
(Police)
That felt good!
Miss, are you okay?
When are we leaving?
There's one more important thing.
I knew it.
Hey,
I've got your back.
Whatever I want to do,
you'll help me, right?
I've got nothing left to lose.
If I can help you
complete the things
on your wish list,
that counts as atonement.
When are we leaving?
(1705)
(1706)
(It's you.)
Judging by how moldy the food is,
he left about two days ago.
Liang,
we traced the drone's registration.
Who is it?
Su Qingchen.
Su Qingchen?
The drone was registered
in a victim's name?
Has Su Qingchen's family
had any large deposits recently?
Yes. I was about to tell you.
Three days ago,
her father deposited $50,000 in one go.
I didn't have the courage
to tell you before.
They avenged us
and gave me life-saving money.
They're not a bad person.
The drone was registered under her name,
but I operated it.
She was innocent.
I'll go with you.
Mr. Su,
For now,
we're not calling you accomplices.
We'll find out the truth.
We won't unfairly blame you.
(Evidence Packaging Bag)
(Get treatment, live well.)
♪Moonlight soaks the withered sunflower♪
That felt great!
Did you see how pathetic Liu Sanhao was?
Begging for mercy, worse off than a dog.
After we pull off this last job,
I'll take you to a place
where no one can find us.
By then,
you'll be my own sister.
For the rest of my life,
I'll work like a horse for you
and protect you!
Where will we go?
Anywhere.
You decide.
Then let's go to a place
where all grudges
can be wiped clean.
♪The sunflower bows, reciting names♪
♪Each petal is a solemn phrase♪
♪And moonlight♪
♪Forever fair♪
♪Lights up crime and punishment♪
♪Sunset washes over the old wall♪
♪Milk tea cools on the stone steps♪
♪Sea wind tugs at your sleeve♪
♪Unspoken words just flee and fade♪
♪The marks on the desk
have faded yellow♪
♪I turned around, and a gunshot rang out♪
♪No one can truly feel another's pain♪
♪The wind is cold,
a fading shadow sways♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪A bullet pierces the spring night♪
♪You sink into the vast crowd♪
♪Years later, when we meet again♪
♪Don't mention this moonlit night♪
♪The waves smooth
two lines of footprints♪
♪Half a cup of sweetness
sinks into the sand♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪Wind back to shore,
clouds back to hills♪
♪We stop here in this night♪
♪This is the past, the only,
the last look back♪
♪One gunshot echoes through half a life♪